

+92.302.2828469

✓ ahmeddilshad545@gmail.com

Karachi, Pakistan

## **Summary**

Male Nurse with 5+ years of experience providing quality care to a wide variety of patients. Possesses a Diploma in general nursing and currently working as male nursing in Iftikhar Memorial Hospital. Aiming to leverage my experience and knowledge to effectively fill the nursing position at your hospital.

### **Skills**

Compassion

Critical Thinking

Pay Close Attention to Detail

Professionalism

• Time Management

# **Experience**

#### Male Nurse

Iftikhar Memorial Hospital, Karachi, Pakistan

Jan 2020 - Present

• Provide direct quality care to patients including daily monitoring, recording, and evaluating of medical conditions of up to 40 patients per shift

#### Male Nurse

Khalida Hospital, Karachi, Pakistan

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Developed and direct a rotational system in managing the care of patients in the department

#### Male Nurse

Nehal Hospital Malir, Karachi, Pakistan

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

- Assisted physicians in taking blood pressure, measuring heartbeat, and recording vitals in physical examinations
- Collaborated with 2 other nursing staff in maintaining a calm environment in caring for patients

#### Male Nurse

Madina Medical Center, Khairpur Mirs, Khair Pur Mir, Pakistan

Jan 2015 - Dec 2016

- Provide direct quality care to patients including daily monitoring, recording, and evaluating of medical conditions of up to 50 patients per day
- Developed and direct a rotational system in managing the care of patients in the department
- Coordinate workforce management objectives with a focus on individual, departmental, and hospital-wide initiatives
- Interact and communicate with patients of all ages and ethnic backgrounds, giving quality medical care and treatment

## **Education**

## **Shah Abdul Latif University**

BSc 2020

# **本 Languages**

SindhiUrduEnglishExpertExpertIntermediate